Guide to the Chiron Review Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Chiron Review records
1960-2015
1900-2015
YCAL MSS 836
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
110.43
(145 boxes) + 5 record album storage
The Chiron Review Records contain submissions to the Chiron Review from poets, other writers, and artists, with related correspondence and subjects files; drafts, proofs, and paper and negative film mechanical layouts for Chiron Review issues, 1989-2011, some with related correspondence, photographs, and notes; similar materials for Chiron Review chapbooks; printed issues of The Kindred Spirit, Chiron Review, and chapbooks; papers relating to Poetry Rendevous events; accounts, mailing lists, and other administrative records; correspondence of Michael Hathaway relating to Chiron Review, his writing, literary colleagues, and friendships; diaries, poetry, and other writings of Hathaway; scrapbooks about poets and the history of Chiron Review; photographs of poets; manuscripts and ephemera removed from books owned by Hathaway; memorabilia and other objects associated with Chiron Review; audiocassettes and videocassettes of poetry events, including some interviews with Hathaway; vinyl sound disks, audiocassettes, and CDs of music performances, most sent by musicians to Hathaway; and digital media, most 3.5 inch computer disks and CDs, containing submissions for Chiron Review, drafts of issues, email correspondence, administrative files, and writings by Hathaway.
Chiron Review
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 15-16, 18-20, 27-31, 46-50, 75-77, 100, 103, 121-124, 128, 148, 150 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 52, 78, 101, 104, 125 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 14, 105, 149 (computer disks and audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
17, 32, 51, 102, 143 (Record album storage): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Arrangement
Organized into eight groupings: April 1994 Acquisition; March 1996 Acquisition; October 1999 Acquisition; November 2002 Acquisition; March 2006 Acquisition; April 2011 Acquisition; Other Acquisitions; and January 2016 Acquisition.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Michael Hathaway and Chiron, Inc. on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, Sinclair Lewis Fund, Ezra Pound Archive Fund, and the Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, 1994-2016.
Michael Hathaway (1961-)
American poet; editor of Chiron Review, 1982-2005 and 2008-2011, and the Chiron Review poetry chapbook series, 1987-1994; and organizer of Poetry Rendevous, a poetry reading event founded at the Great Bend Public Library, Kansas, in 1988.
Chiron Review
Quarterly journal of poetry, other fiction, nonfiction, photography, and art, published in St. John, Kansas, 1982-2005 and 2008-2011. Founded as The Kindred Spirit by Michael Hathaway and his mother, assistant editor Jane Hathaway, the title was changed to Chiron Review in 1989. Publication was suspended following issue 81 (winter 2005), resumed with issue 82 (spring 2008), and has been suspended indefinitely since issue 94 (2011 spring). Chiron Review published a series of poetry chapbooks, 1987-1994.
Scope and Contents
The Chiron Review Records contain submissions to the Chiron Review from poets, other writers, and artists, with related correspondence and subjects files; drafts, proofs, and paper and negative film mechanical layouts for Chiron Review issues, 1989-2011, some with related correspondence, photographs, and notes; similar materials for Chiron Review chapbooks; printed issues of The Kindred Spirit, Chiron Review, and chapbooks; papers relating to Poetry Rendevous events; accounts, mailing lists, and other administrative records; correspondence of Michael Hathaway relating to Chiron Review, his writing, literary colleagues, and friendships; diaries, poetry, and other writings of Hathaway; scrapbooks about poets and the history of Chiron Review; photographs of poets; manuscripts and ephemera removed from books owned by Hathaway; memorabilia and other objects associated with Chiron Review; audiocassettes and videocassettes of poetry events, including some interviews with Hathaway; vinyl sound disks, audiocassettes, and CDs of music performances, most sent by musicians to Hathaway; and digital media, most 3.5 inch computer disks and CDs, containing submissions for Chiron Review, drafts of issues, email correspondence, administrative files, and writings by Hathaway.
Chiron review; American literature -- 20th Century -- Periodicals; American literature -- 21st century -- Periodicals; American poetry -- 20th Century -- Periodicals; American poetry -- 21st century -- Periodicals; Authors and publishers -- United States; Periodical editors -- United States; Little magazines -- United States; Poets, American -- 20th Century; Poets, American -- 21st century; Publishers and publishing -- United States; Audiocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 21st century; Born digital -- United States -- 20th Century; Born digital -- United States -- 21st century; Drawings (visual works) -- United States -- 20th Century; Drawings (visual works) -- United States -- 21st century; Long-playing records -- United States -- 20th Century; Memorabilia -- United States -- 20th Century; Memorabilia -- United States -- 21st century; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs -- United States -- 21st century; Videocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Periodical editors -- United States -- 20th Century; Periodical editors -- United States -- 21st century; Poets -- United States -- 20th Century; Poets -- United States -- 21st century; Hathaway, Michael, 1961-
- April 1994 Acquisition, 1986-1994, undated; 15.41; (19 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 14-16 (audiovisual material): Restricted Fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 44 (Box 1)
    - Unsorted, 39 (Box 2)
    - Unsorted, 58 (Box 3)
    - Unsorted, 41 (Box 4)
    - Unsorted, 30 (Box 5)
    - Unsorted, 41 (Box 6)
    - Unsorted, 30 (Box 7)
    - Unsorted, 48 (Box 8)
    - Unsorted, 5 (Box 9)
  - Chiron Review Issues
    - Kindred Spirit 8 (1986 February 19) - 14 (1987 winter) (microfilm), 2 (Box 10)
    - Chiron Review 18 (1989 spring) - 33 (1992 winter) (microfilm), 4 (Box 10)
    - Chiron Review 29 (1991 winter) (Box 9)
    - Chiron Review 32 (1992 autumn) (Box 9)
    - Chiron Review 33 (1992 winter) (Box 9)
    - Chiron Review 36 (1993 autumn), 4 (Box 9)
    - Chiron Review 37/38 (1994 spring), 7 (Box 9)
  - Chiron Review Chapbooks
    Related Materials
    See also: Other Writings subseries
    - Catlin, Alan. A Ghost Story (Box 9)
    - Dweller, Cliff. The Persistence of Desire, 2 (Box 9)
    - Edwards, Connie. The Girl That Time Passed By (Box 9)
    - Foster, Susannah. Earthbound in Betty Grable's Shoes (Box 9)
    - Glade, Jon Forrest. Photographs of the Jungle, 3 (Box 9)
    - Heim, Scott. Saved from Drowning, 2 (Box 9)
    - Holt, Rochelle. Author's Choice (Box 9)
    - Holt, Rochelle. In the Mist and the Fog (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Marael. Mad Woman, Bad Reputation (Box 9)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. The Loca Viuda, Let Loose (Box 11)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. Tilting the Planet (Box 11)
    - Lifshin, Lyn. Many Madonnas (Box 11)
    - Long, Virginia Love. All Roads Lead to Bushy Fork, 2 (Box 11)
    - Long, Virginia Love. Squaw Winter, 2 (Box 11)
    - Malley, Kathleen. Wild Heart (Box 11)
    - Morris, Peter. Fountains Dyed Blue for the Day, 2 (Box 11)
    - Peters, Robert. Love Poems for Robert Mitchum, 2 (Box 11)
    - Zeiser, Linda. Chain of Fools (Box 11)
  - Writings by Michael Hathaway
    - Diary, 1986-1988 (Box 11)
    - Diary, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Diary, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Diary, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Diary, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - Diary, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
    - Diary, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Diary, 1992-1993 (Box 12)
    - "The Adventures of Fred and Mellia" (Box 12)
    - "Dogcatcher's Lament" (Box 12)
    - God Poems (Box 12)
    - "Inconspicuous" (Box 12)
    - "Puddle of Stars" (Box 12)
    - Stumbling into Light, 5 (Box 12)
    - Unidentified (Box 12)
  - Other Writings
    - Johnson, Marael. "Mad Woman, Bad Reputation", 2 (Box 12)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Loca Vida" (Box 12)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Tilting the Planet" (Box 12)
    - Morris, Peter. "Fountains", 3 (Box 12)
    - Nelson, Michael. "Strange Rituals of the Living" (Box 12)
    - Peters, Robert. "Love Poems for Robert Mitchum", 2 (Box 12)
    - Subraman, Belinda. Unidentified (Box 12)
    - Unidentified, 7 (Box 12)
    - Unidentified, 3 (Box 13)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    Boxes 14-16 (audiovisual material), 17 (Record album storage), and boxes 18-20 (digital and audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Unidentified, 2 (Box 13)
    - Computer media, 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      Box 14: Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - [no label information], 1994-ycal-0315-a-0001; 1 (Box 14)
    - Sempsell, Kevin Patrick. "Family Val-U Pack", 1992; 1; 00:34:47; The program is distorted at times. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002099363419)
      Scope and Contents
      A booklet detailing the works on this audiocassette are included.
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Moffeit, Tony. "Outlaw" performance poetry blues, A Stone River Production, 1990; YCALMSS836_0001; 1; 00:09:24 (Box 14, Item barcode 39002102317147)
    - Moffeit, Tony. "'Mad Man' Junkyard Blues," A Stone River Production, 1990; YCALMSS836_0002; 1; 00:14:19 (Box 14, Item barcode 39002102317154)
    - Albertano, Linda J. "Skin", undated; 1; 00:42:07; Static can be heard on the tape. An echo can also be heard in the audio. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363252)
      A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
      Side A / Side B
      "Skin of the Western World"
      "The Death of Kong"
      "Jazz and Jurisprudence"
      "Valentine's Day with Lucifer"
      "Being History"
      "Shame"
      "Nero at the Barbeque"
      "To the Pacific"
    - Armstrong, Glen and the Dirty Clergy. "Under a Van Gogh Sky", 1990; 1; 00:34:59 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363260)
      A list of contents with this audiocassette is included.
      "One Last Song About the Moon"
      "Hollywood"
      "Love Songs"
      "Can't Stand the Heat"
      "Walking Home Alone"
      "Too Much Junky Business"
      "Trying to Get the Devil to Appraise Her Soul"
      "Diamonds in Her Head"
      "Scene Tucked Under a Van Gogh Sky"
      "Whispering Voices"
    - Bogen, Laurel Ann. "Vulnerable Street", 1989; 1; 00:16:38 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363278)
      Side 1 / Side 2
      "Origami" (1:39)
      "Rat City" (3:48)
      "Loot" (2:12)
      "Song for Brian" (2:39)
      "Vulnerable Street" (:54)
      "Jive Artiste Speaks Out on Frustration" (2:19)
      "All the Earnest young Men" (2:15)
      "The Room" (1:08)
    - "A Century of Australian Verse (Best of Australian Poetry)", 1992 April; 1; 00:55:54 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363286)
      A list of contents are included with this audiocassette. There is also a note that reads: For Michael Hathaway...Happy Easter...4/92...Love and Blessings from My Homeland...Julie Ball...
      "Bell Birds"
      "Domestic Poem"
      "Burning Off a Traveler"
      "Australia"
      "Triste, Triste"
      "The Year of the Foxes"
      "Merry-Go-Round"
      "Down from the Country"
      "Where the Dead Men Lie"
      "The Approval"
      "Cock Crow"
      "Developing a Wife"
      "Eye to Her Daughters"
      "Profiles of my Father"
      "The Future"
      "Andy's Gone with Cattle"
      "Nationality"
      "Remembering the Rural Life"
      "Parents"
      "Letter"
      "Who Points the Swallow"
      "The Sick Assailant"
      "Summer Sketches Sydney"
      "Suburban Sonnet Boxing Day"
      "Butterfly"
      "There are Some Lusty Voices Singing"
      "Grit: A Doxology"
      "Old Woman in Apple Country"
      "A Sporting Elegy Rod Laver"
      "Drifters"
      "Late Ferry"
      "A History of the Future..."
    - Coleman, Wanda. "High Priestess of Word", undated; 1; 01:00:29; An echo can be heard at times on the tape. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363294)
      "Dolls"
      "Dolls 2"
      "Angel Baby Blues"
      "Mr. Lopez"
      "Fat Lena"
      "Ms. Sambo + the Tigers"
      "Without Visible Means"
      "Wanda Why Aren't You Dead"
      "Blues in the Night"
      "Day of Remembrance"
      "Emmett Till"
      "Letter to Big Joe"
      "I Love the Dark"
    - Fried, Elliot. "The Man who Owned Cars", 1994; 1; 00:41:23; An echo can be heard at times on the tape. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363302)
      "The Man Who Owned Cars"
      "Mesquite Flats Campsite, Death Valley"
      "Traffic Report"
      "Souls"
      "You Can Get There From Here"
      "Chain Mail"
      "As If There Were No Such Thing as Death"
      "Campground"
      "The Town of Haiku"
      "Backing In"
      "Interstate 80"
      "Target Transaction"
      "Doing the Laundry"
      "Poem City"
      "Winnebago Sutra"
      "Why I Want to be the Next Poet Laureate"
      "CNN"
      "Please Recycle This"
      "Circle K"
      "Daily I Fall in Love with Waitresses"
      "Tour"
    - Gehman, Pleasant. "Ruined", undated; 1; 00:57:22; An echo can be heard at times on the tape. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363310)
      "Contents of Purse, January 1992"
      "Season of the Witch"
      "The Wild West Club"
      "Working Girl"
      "1,000 Times"
      "Queen of the Three Clubs"
      "Sunland"
      "Way Out West"
      "Cookin' with Ray"
      "Esther's Orbit Room -- Hangover -- Ester's Orbit Room Revisited"
      "Lifeguard"
      "Red Devil"
      "What I Got For My Birthday, March 17, 1992"
      "They Lived Across the Street..."
      "Know Your Drug Addicts: Parts I, II, III"
      "White Trash Apocalypse"
      "Somewhere Over the Rainbow"
      "The Man Upstairs"
      "The Tamarind Arms"
      "Las Estrellas"
    - Gypsy 16. "Audio Arts Review", 1991; 1; 01:00:59 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363328)
      "Ice Curtains, Bar"
      "The Last Poet, Lies and Gossip, Poem for Evelyn, I Mean"
      "Dancing in Quicksand, Bloodshot Angels"
      "Lady of the Valentine"
      "We are Here, Avec Vache, Automobiles, Clockwork"
      "Lettre À Sophie, L'Exil Penchant Sur Moi Les Longs Cils De Son Rêve
      "And, So to Hell, The World Saved on Labor Day, Hill Nights"
      "Im Baloon"
      "Nuthatch in the Rain"
      "First Lover"
      "Confuses, Revelation"
      "Airbourne, Sequential Scissors"
    - "Ken/Edna E. St. V. Millay, C.K. [DeRueris] reading", 1989; 1; 01:03:23; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363336)
    - "Letter from Lori Steinberg, ed or Wormfeast; Letter 2 Hathaway", 1993 January 29; 1; 01:19:30; High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. An echo can be heard at times on the tape. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363351)
    - Lipman, Joel. "Down Your Street", undated; 1; 00:56:47 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363369)
      "They All Kiss the Feet"
      "November 24th, 1963"
      "I Saw the Kansas Comet Streak Across the Earth"
      "A Day in the Park, 1969"
      "One Name Not on the Wall"
      "Why I Give Bums Money"
      "I Lived Your Life for Three Days Once"
      "Revolutionary Cinderella"
      "The Day I Had Love"
      "Rerun on the McAllister #5"
      "Love at a Thai Cafe"
      "A Foggy Day in London Town"
      "Ode to Rudy Ray Moore"
      "Late, at the Night Club"
      "Meanwhile, at the House of Death"
      "The Phone F**k"
      "June Street (A Suite in Five Parts): The Rains, Waiting, The Telephone, Bondage, Truth"
      "Up from the Trailer Park"
      "Genevieve Lost in the Night"
      "Damn the Radio"
      "The Kipe Artist's Love Song"
      "Amid the Vietnamese"
      "If I Could Cry"
      "In a Small Hotel on Sutter Street"
      "Down Your Street"
      "Tell Me It Ain't a Game"
    - Mohr, Bill. "Vehemence", undated; 1; 00:55:14; An echo can be heard at times on the tape. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363344)
      "Act 1: The Rival"
      "Pancho's Tacos"
      "Earthquake"
      "Naked Chef"
      "Your Skin"
      "Many Years"
      "Cro-Magnon"
      "Rival"
      "Sunset Blvd."
      "Tough to Please"
      "Act 2: Vehemence"
      "The Drop"
      "Canvas"
      "Doubleheader"
      "Complexities"
      "Odd Duck"
      "Obsenity Oath"
      "Navy Brat"
      "Flooding the Engine"
      "Tattoo"
      "Vehemence"
      "An Answer"
      "Broadcasting"
      "Orbison"
      "Act 3: Heart of the World"
      "Trampolinists"
      "Kites"
      "Apt. No. 6"
      "Fire Shadow"
      "Scorpio"
      "The Other"
      "Landscape"
      "Nameless Dread"
      "Contestant"
      "Candles/Wishes"
      "Sotel 13"
      "Monk"
      "Radio Solitude"
      "Heart of World"
      "Good Weight"
      "Growing Poems, Grown"
    - "Sanctuary 5", 1985; 1; 00:58:12 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363377)
      "Kenneth I Think" with Catfish
      "A Far Cry from Spring" - Larry Conklin
      "Are You Going to Kill Me?" - Steve Grandell
      "The End of Passion" and "Nun Meet the Prostitute" - James Starr
      "Job Adventure Poem" - Patrick McKinnon
      "Rot" - Mark Tucker
      Excerpt from "Ursonata" - Lenny Bove
      "Ganges Sunrise" - Owen Davis with Chas, Dickie & Cathy Stevens
      "Sestorak in Kantanka" - Tine Rozanc
      "The People Waiting" - Todd Moore
      "It Was a Peaceful Night" and "Cowboy Afraid of Women and Horses" - Tom House
      Excerpt from "Relationships" - Richard Kostelanetz
      "Total Eclipse" - Face in the Crowd
      "Patriotic Poem" and "Mindlessness Over Matter" - Gerald Locklin
      "Old Spain/Traumatic Mouth" - Belinda Subraman & Ken Clinger
      "Jasper/Are You Having a Good Time?" - Lenny Bove
    - Subraman, Belinda & Friends. Untitled, 1985; 1; 00:31:16; The program is distorted at times. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363385)
    - "Tabula Rasa: Contemporary Literature, Volume 2, No. 1", 1992; 1; 01:29:29; A warble can be heard during the program. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363393)
    - Voss, Fred. Reading selected poems from his book Goodstone, 1991; 1; 00:54:26; From 54:30 until the end of the tape, the right channel is recorded at a lower level and there is cross talk. (Box 15, Item barcode 39002099363401)
    - Werner, Connie Lorraine. (music) "Poetry Rendezvous", 1988 August 14; 1; 00:20:22; High frequency background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 16, Item barcode 39002099362676)
    - Winson, Robert. "Poetry Devils", 1989; 1; 00:39:34 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002099362684)
    - Z., Bob. "Prisoncamp Reality", 1992; 1; 00:33:22 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002099362692)
    - "Breaking Things", 1 33 1/3 vinyl sound disk (Box 17 (Record album storage))
    - "Sheen", 1 45 vinyl sound disk (Box 17 (Record album storage))
    - The Criminal Mind. "Gone", 1 33 1/3 vinyl sound disk (Box 17 (Record album storage))
    - Holt, Rochelle. "Yellow Pears Smooth as Silk", 1 78 vinyl sound disk (Box 17 (Record album storage))
    - Abbe, Steve. "Jerusalem Donuts", 1 CD (Box 18)
    - Albertano, Linda J. "Skin", 1 CD (Box 18)
    - Bisi, Martin. "All Will Be Won", 1 CD (Box 18)
    - Blackmadrid. "Atlantic Crossing: the People's Journey", 1 CD (Box 18)
    - The Blue Humans; Rudolph Grey. "Clear to Higher Time", 1 CD (Box 18)
    - Gehman, Pleasant. "Ruined", 1 CD (Box 19)
    - Ginn, Greg. "Dick", 1 CD (Box 19)
    - "Innings and Quarters", 1 CD (Box 19)
    - Lipman, Joel. "Down Your Street", 1 CD (Box 19)
    - "M-3", 1 CD (Box 19)
    - Northup, Harry C. "Personal Crime", 1 CD (Box 20)
    - Mohr, Bill. "Vehemence", 1 CD (Box 20)
    - "Overpass", 1 CD (Box 20)
    - Richardson, Scott. "Tornado Souvenirs", 1 CD (Box 20)
    - Weizmann, Danny. "The Wet Dog Shakes", 1 CD (Box 20)
  - Other Papers
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Manuscripts removed from books, 6 (Box 13)
    - Unidentified (Box 13)
- March 1996 Acquisition, 1994-1995, undated; 8.34; (11 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Box 27 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Jackson, Lorri, 6 (Box 21)
    - Jackson, Lorri. "Lorri Jackson/from Oberc 02/12/95", 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
      Restricted Fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Unsorted, 29 (Box 21)
    - Unsorted, 36 (Box 22)
    - Unsorted, 6 (Box 23)
  - Chiron Review Issues
    - Chiron Review 39 (1994 summer), 4 (Box 23)
    - Chiron Review 40 (1994 autumn), 4 (Box 23)
    - Chiron Review 41 (1994 winter), 6 (Box 23)
    - Chiron Review 42 (1995 spring), 4 (Box 23)
    - Chiron Review 45 (1995 summer), 5 (Box 23)
    - Chiron Review 44-45 (1995 winter), 8 (Box 24)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Chiron Review Chapbooks
    - Cunningham, Elizabeth. The Wild Mother (Box 24)
    - Edwards, Connie. The Girl that Time Passed By (Box 24)
    - Gessen, Masha, editor. Half a Revolution: Contemporary Fiction by Russian Women (Box 24)
    - Hathaway, Jane. My Angel & Other Poems (Box 24)
    - Hathaway, Michael, editor. Poetry Rendezvous '95 Anthology, 2 (Box 24)
    - Holt, Rochelle. The Driver's Shadow (Box 24)
    - Holt, Rochelle. Panes: Fiction as Therapy (Box 24)
    - Holt, Rochelle. Jokers are Wild (Box 24)
    - Johnson, Marael. Mad Woman: Trois, 3 (Box 24)
    - Long, Virginia Love. Poems (Box 24)
    - Lynn, Catherine. The Snake Pit (Box 25)
    - Madhouse Poems (Box 25)
    - Mahlsdorf, Charlotte von. I am My Own Woman: The Outlaw Life of Charlotte von Mahlsdorf, Berlin's Most Distinguished Transvestite, 2 (Box 25)
    - McDaniel, Wilma Elizabeth. Man With a Star Quilt (Box 25)
    - Schmid, Vernon. Unidentified (Box 25)
    - Unidentified, 5 (Box 25)
  - Writings by Michael Hathaway
    - God Poems (Box 25)
    - Ratboy, Etc., 2 (Box 25)
    - Ratboy's Poetry, Etc., 1995 February (Box 25)
    - Stumbling into Light, 2 (Box 25)
  - Other Writings
    - McDaniel, Wilma Elizabeth. "The Ketchup Bottle", 2 (Box 25)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    Boxes 27-31 and 32 (Record album storage) (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Androla, Ron. "Goop", 1994 August; 1; 01:34:51; The program is distorted at times. A warble can be heard during the program. The program is recorded over pre-existing content. High frequency interference is on the tape. Static can be heard on the tape. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363237)
      This audiocassette contains a list of contents.
      "Amerika Hates Me"
      "Goop"
      "Happy Happy Heroin"
      "Bowel!"
      "Tanks for Beer"
      "Tanks for Mammary"
      "Joe's Suicide"
      "Sex in Your Ear"
      "Amerika uff Amerika"
      "Not Fishing"
      "A Problem with Coffee"
      "The Great Fuck You of our Society"